

IELAIZA ELLENSBURG

Application Developer

PROFILE

I am one of the team members and also the team captain of the Sranan Techies (Creative Tech Hub) team, which participates in competitions and represents Suriname. My team and I develop applications with innovative ideas and solutions.

My interest in participating in competitions is driven by my desire to apply and further develop my skills and qualities. Additionally, I see this opportunity as a chance to contribute to the movement toward equal representation of women in the IT sector.

I am currently a student at NATIN MBO, where I am in my fourth year specializing in ICT with a focus on application development.

+5

+597 867 3083



ielaizaellensburg@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Ellensburg

First Names: lelaiza Antoinette Erwinne Eugenie

Date of birth: 23 - 02 - 2004
Place of birth: Paramaribo
Gender: Vrouw

Address: Konsaistraat #6
City: Tammenga
Phone number: +597 867 3083

Marital Status: Ongehuwd
Nationality: Surinaamse

REFERENCES

N.V. VERENIGDE SURINAAMSE HOLDINGMIJ

Email address: hrm@vshunited.com

SKILLS

Analytical	70%
Creativity	88%
Innovative	70%
Planning and organizing	81%
Flexibility	75%
Teamwork	88%



IELAIZA ELLENSBURG

Application Developer

Hobbies

- Dancer
- Youtuber
- Homework tutor
- Skincare specialist
- Student coach

Expertise

- Customer-friendly
- Stress-resistant
- Perseverance
- Assertive
- Communication skills
- Leadership
- +597 867 3083
- ielaizaellensburg@gmail.com
- Konsaistraat #6, Kasabaholoweg

EDUCATION

Maria Hartmann School - GLO

2010 - 2016

Possessing a diploma

W.S.R. Ritfeld School - MULO

2016 - 2020

Possessing a diploma

NATIN Infrastructuur - MBO

2020 - 2021

Possessing a report

NATIN ICT - MBO

2021 - heden

To be obtained

WORK EXPERIENCE

VSH United N.V. VERENIGDE SURINAAMSE HOLDINGMIJ ICT employee

03 - 04 - 2023 until 20 - 07 - 2023

During my internship, I had to perform my core tasks on the work floors for the role of ICT employee. VLBTO - diploma still to be received.

Crea+her Girls in ICT 2024 Hackathon was held in Jamaica

17 - 04 - 2024 until 25 - 04 -2024

An opportunity to apply and further develop my skills and qualities. Additionally, a movement towards equal representation of women in the IT sector. As team Sranan Techies, we ended up in 4th place

CANTO Innovation Challenge will be held in Curação

29 - 04 - 2024 tot heden

Tijdens mijn stage periode moest ik mijn kerntaken uit oefenen op de werkvloeren voor de functie ICT medewerker. VLBTO - diploma nog in ontvangst krijgen.